After New Year, entrance exams
for private schools will finally begin.
Make sure you keep studying until then.
Winter break starts next week.
I'm going to graduate soon!
T-there's no time left!
So what's this important stuff
you're going to talk about?
Listen carefully.
Kijibayashi and I will graduate
in three months.
There will only be
Inukawa and Saruta left.
That would naturally mean Brainwave Club
is going to be terminated.
Isn't that just sad?
-What's so sad about it?
-Huh?
We're not going to make
any memories at this rate.
Think back to everything we did so far!
But we have some memories,
like eating snacks and chatting
while lazing around.
There's also playing cards and games.
No, I'm not talking about
that kind of stuff.
-Huh?
Huh?
Wait, what?
Why are you crying?
Is your stomach hurting?
Did your exam go that badly?
I mean, I'm no better, but...
We didn't make any progress
on our research for telepathy!
This is our only chance!
Is it something worth crying over?
Y-you can try better
at high school, right?
So, you were actually serious about
wanting to communicate with aliens?
Of course I am...
I'm also going to continue it as a hobby.
But this is the only time where I get
to spend time with you guys.
You guys are the only ones who would
join a club with this weird goal.
This place is a special place for me!
Hey, what do you guys think?
Well, uhh...
What do you think, Inukawa?
Well, uhh, let's hear from
the youngest first.
Umm, telepathy is...
Sorry, what was our goal again?
Wow, incredible lung capacity...
Thank you for everything, you three.
The Brainwave Club is hereby disbanded.
It was pretty fun.
Wait, we're really disbanded?
Seems like Kurata is way more serious
about this than we ever thought.
I guess we should give
all the books in here a read?
(MOB MOB WOW!)
I realized that our youth is gray
The origin of this uneasiness
Is yet unknown
Trains of emotions keep running
Through my brain
Struggling through this adolescence
Don't disturb my deep psyche
Who is that behind you?
Opposing ideas create distortion
Exorcise all the sorrow
So, do what you can now
My life
Finally, break it down
(Want) Both greed
(Young) And honesty
(Burn) Are growing
(1) On this chest of mine
(Trance) I'm not waking up
(Chance) I want to wake up
(Stance) These two different faces of mine
(1) Are standing back-to-back
Taking things as it is
In this free relation where
We resent each other
Once these two become one
That smile becomes one
And only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
(Communicating 1 ~Winter Break~)
Brother.
There's some guests for you.
They're waiting outside.
Who is it?
It seems pretty cold outside.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
It's been a month since
Dimple last showed up.
Is it still bothering you?
Oh, I was just spacing off.
I see.
Huh?
Everyone? What's going on?
Mob! Why didn't you pick up your phone?
We called you several times!
Sorry, I didn't notice.
Did you need something?
Please, can't you use
your powers for telepathy?
We acted as if we knew
while we actually didn't!
We underestimated what
being a youth means!
Inukawa, calm down.
What is going on?
I see, so Tome quit.
I think she's just prioritizing
her entrance exams.
But I can't use telepathy.
Can't you make it work somehow?
Umm, I know someone
that can use telepathy.
Huh?
If the target is the space,
then I'm afraid we can't help.
Our telepathy only works
between us siblings.
I see.
Yeah, of course
it wouldn't be that easy...
But...
We might be able to find other telepaths
if someone stronger helped.
Yeah, but only if there is someone
who can receive our telepathy.
Huh?
It might be impossible to send
a specific message to someone,
but we can spread
a noise around us.
Noise?
It's an unpleasant sound
that only telepaths can hear.
So, something like an ear ringing?
So you're going to call them?
Yes, but it depends on the person
receiving it themselves.
If we keep emitting the noise, they might
try to approach the source of the noise.
But we won't know
what kind of person it is, then?
That's kinda scary, isn't it?
But they're our only hope.
What do we do, Brother?
This is for Tome, right?
Let's do it.
What can I do to help?
He seems really dependable
for some reason...
It's cold here, so how about we first move
to the club room for a strategy meeting?
-Go go go!
-Pass here!
Right now, thank's to Teru's training,
we can communicate up to
three kilometers if we do our best.
I managed to receive the message
to buy natto
on the way home the other day.
You could've just used a phone
rather than trying hard.
But if we fire the noise
in all directions,
then we'll probably only
manage around 500 meters.
That's not very far...
If Kageyama helps
and amplifies our output,
I think we can double
or triple our noise range.
Whoa, that's amazing.
Wait, is Mob's brother also a psychic?!
My brother would be better at this.
Let's give it a try.
I'll try to make it as wide as possible.
Thanks for calling us
for this interesting experiment.
We can finally pay you back,
Kageyama.
All right, let's try this, Kaito.
Yeah. Let's do our best, Brother.
We're currently emitting the noise.
We can't hear anything...
But yeah, do your thing, Mob.
I'm sending some power your way.
Please do.
T-this is amazing!
Even I can faintly hear it.
I-it feels like my head
is about to split open!
I can add some more,
but I guess we shouldn't do that.
It's okay, we'll push it to the limit.
You don't have to push
yourselves that far!
This is the only way!
Please do it!
Whoa, I'm getting goosebumps.
Y-yeah, me too.
Is it affecting the human body?
Who is it?
Whoa, that scared me.
What are you guys doing here?
Oh, it's just Takenaka.
Who is he?
A former member of the Brainwave Club.
The Brainwave Club was abolished
because he quit on us.
Why are you back here now, anyway?
You're in the Tennis Club, right?
Oh, we still have club activities
even on winter break.
They're making us run around
the perimeters in this stupid cold weather.
I mean, that's what you signed up for.
So I waited for a chance to slip away.
I was thinking of taking it easy
in this room.
I knew it, you're actually just like us.
By the way, what are you doing?
We're looking for telepaths.
These people are psychics.
What?
Are you for real?
You guys are still doing
that kind of thing?
That's so stupid!
This is why people think the Brainwave Club
is full of weirdos and creeps.
Get a grip already.
Oh, shut up.
We're just finally getting
serious now, okay?
If you're going to get in our way,
please leave.
Fine, I'll leave once I warm myself a bit.
All right, let's do it one more time.
It was going pretty well.
Yeah, if we do it multiple times
during this winter break,
a real telepath might actually show up.
All right, ready...
...go!
Hey, you self-proclaimed psychics.
What the heck are you guys doing
with such a serious face?
Aren't you guys embarrassed?
It's getting even stronger?
Just a little more push.
Even my head starts to hurt.
Can't you guys just stop...?
What's wrong, Takenaka?
You're looking kinda pale.
Do you have a fever or something?
You're so noisy, goddammit!
Just...
Just stop that noise already.
I find out I'm different from others
when I was five.
The kindergarten teacher's thoughts and
speech are different, but nobody noticed.
Then when I voiced
my father's real thoughts,
my mother broke down crying.
That's when I realized it's not something
I'm supposed to do.
Others' thoughts just simply
came to my head.
As I grew up,
they grow even louder,
and the range from where
I can receive them also grows.
It was such a pain.
I think it was around third grade
when I can send my thoughts to others.
You always carry snacks
with you, that's nice.
I have tons of them back at home.
I'll bring some next time.
-Really? Then I want some crackling gum.
-I'll go shoplifting again.
Are you stupid?
You're going to get arrested!
What's wrong?
Return it to the shop!
O-okay!
After that, to let off some steam,
I assaulted someone by yelling
inside their head every day.
Y-you always lived like that?
I don't do that anymore, Inukawa.
-Wha?!
-What's wrong?
He spoke... directly in my head?
Kijibayashi, Saruta.
Really?
He's kinda scary.
Telepaths are abnormal.
Yeah, I guess so.
I am an abnormal existence.
But don't worry.
I've learned how to keep other's thoughts
from entering my head.
I've had enough of listening to what
others think. It makes me sick.
That's why I always wear an earplug.
I sealed this ability away.
But then I hear this
really stupid loud noise.
Oh, right, sorry about that.
We're looking for telepaths.
Will you help us?
Why now?
You're not actually interested
in telepathy, right?
No, we're serious here!
You'll know it's true
if you read our thoughts!
I don't want to make any more
bad memories with telepathy.
I'm not going to take off
my earplug either.
Go ask someone else.
You were looking for friends,
didn't you?
What?
You joined this club
because you thought there might
be someone like you, right?
Yeah, that's right.
But that was a mistake.
It's just some occult research club.
That's why I stopped having the faint hope
that there is someone else like me.
I have no plan of being used to make
some "fun memories" for you people.
Being used...
If you think that's all there is to it,
then it's okay if you don't want to help.
That is, if you really aren't interested.
What are you trying to say?
I also have times when
I'm fed up with my powers.
Even if I try to hide it,
it's still an inseparable part of me.
If there are others that need your powers,
then I think accepting their request
can sometimes be enjoyable.
What's with the high and mighty act?
Don't act like you know me.
It's my true feeling.
W-well, I don't want you
to make that noise again.
I guess I'll help, just this once.
Thanks! We'll be in your debt,
Takenaka!
-Yay!
-We did it!
-Thanks a lot, you two!
Takenaka.
Did you... read my brother's mind?
You're his little brother, huh?
Now then, did I?
You have a complex about not being able
to relate with your brother?
Is that what my thoughts are saying?!
Nah, I'm just guessing.
I have my earplugs, but I can still
guess somewhat from your eyes.
I think those kinds of things
should be cherished.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Here.
It's a purifying kelp tea that we've
just begun accepting mail-order recently.
Winter also affects those
kinds of spiritual things,
so please make sure
to keep yourself hydrated.
Dehydration leads
to poor blood circulation,
so it might invite evil spirits that cause
fatigue and poor sleeping habits.
Ooh...
Thank you very much.
I will visit you again, Master Reigen.
Even my body feels sluggish.
It's hard to get any motivation
when it's this cold, yeah?
What are you doing?
It's homework from school.
I have to finish it during winter break.
Winter break, huh?
Being a student sure is nice,
having events like that and all.
How about we go drinking for once?
Sorry, I have a year-end party
with friends from night school today.
I see...
Oh, Mob? What's wrong?
Plans for New Year's Eve?
I don't have any for now.
Are you going on a shrine visit
on New Year?
What?
Mud Boat Mountain?
UFO?
Fine, fine. I'll do it.
I gotta go for some UFO searching
at the end of the year.
They called me just so they
could get me to rent a car.
Man, why do I have to babysit
on New Year's Eve?
I'm happy for you, Reigen.
What? Mud Boat Mountain?
I'm not going.
Got a winter training camp
with my cram school.
The Brainwave Club is already
disbanded anyway,
just do whatever you want.
She said she isn't coming...
Seriously, President Kurata?
I guess we just have to keep
inviting her until New Year's Eve.
She'll definitely agree eventually.
However, President Kurata stopped
answering her phone after that.
And so, New Year's Eve arrives.
That's a weirdly nice sleep,
I even woke up on my own...
Huh?
It ran out of batteries?!
You got to be kidding me!
I lectured Mob to always be punctual,
and now look at me!
What, Tome isn't coming?
Yeah...
We ended up losing contact with her.
But I'm sure she'll be happy
if we show her some UFO photos.
You're right.
We've made it this far,
let's make sure we find those UFOs.
She's actually here.
Faster than anybody else, to boot.
What's this all about,
President Kurata?
What about your training camp?
Yeah, I'm skipping that.
What, am I not supposed to be here?
No, but...
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Oh, that? I broke my phone,
so I didn't realize.
The heck?
So, who's the telepath you guys found?
She still doesn't know?
Yeah, I thought she wouldn't
come if we told her.
The meeting time is 9 AM, right?
Let's wait for a little bit.
Right, they're totally not coming.
Why won't he pick up his phone?!
Is it okay to make
your master wait this long?
I'm not sure.
I sent a message telling
the situation earlier,
but he didn't reply.
We might have to call this off...
You're so freaking late, Takenaka!
My bad, I overslept.
Takenaka?
What the heck are you doing here?
Sorry I'm late.
President Kurata.
I'm the telepath.
What?
What is this?
Are you guys messing with me?
Well, now that everyone's here,
let's head to the parking lot.
Run for it!!
Hurry up! He might be angry
and already left!
He's here!
I'm sorry we took a while, Master.
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's New Year's Eve,
let's take it easy.
He just arrived two minutes ago.
O-okay, let's go.
Please drive safely.
Please don't talk for a while.
How could you oversleep on
an important day like this?
I had a hard time sleeping.
Was others' thought too loud again?
No, I was nervous.
It's been a while since
I've done anything like this.
I see.
-President, do you want some gum?
-Hmph, no.
Can't believe you guys
actually tricked me.
Takenaka's a telepath? Hah.
-No, he's the real deal.
-It's okay.
I don't even know if I can call
a UFO or not either.
Approaching destination.
Oh, so this is the place?
It's Mud Boat Mountain.
It's going to be full of winding
mountain roads from here.
Don't get carsick before
we find the UFO, okay?
The blue light shined
Dazzling my eye at 01:30 AM
Even as I swiped the page over,
The smiles of friends besides me remain
Yes, I want someone to understand
All the colorless and transparent wishes
All the breath stuck within
The depth of my heart
Suddenly flowed out
Bringing my consciousness back
I remember the days hung dry
The very normal days passed by
Even if reality is corrupted
The sky we saw together
Was definitely real
It's harder to understand than
The grammar on the blackboard
The story that disappears
Under 24 hours makes me sad and lonely
It's so hard, and I find myself
On the verge of giving up again and again
But I...
The current me will no longer give up
Overflowing emotions on my sleeve,
Running through worry and doubt
Nobody has decided
if the future is 0 or 100,
So I'll paint over them myself
Even if my existence itself
can't be proven,
If this world struck me in my heart
I will flood it with cobalt blue
Hysteria from carsickness
and forgetting to bring things.
Many things happened,
but we reached the summit.
Now, time to show the power
of the Brainwave Club!
Next on episode eight of
Mob Psycho 100 III,
"Communicating 2
~Close Encounters of the Third Kind~"
Watching from overseas?
Of course, that is a wise decision.